[{"name":"Level 1","stageID":1,"roundList":[{"sentence":"안녕하세요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"Hello.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"Thanks.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Nice to meet you.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"고맙습니다.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"Nice to meet you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Hello.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"만나서 반가워요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"Nice to meet you.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"Hello.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"Hello.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"안녕하세요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"고맙습니다.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 사과를 먹어요.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"Thank you.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"안녕하세요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"고맙습니다.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 사과를 먹어요.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"Nice to meet you.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"안녕하세요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"고맙습니다.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"만나서 반갑습니다.","isCorrect":true}]}]},{"name":"Level 2","stageID":2,"roundList":[{"sentence":"내 이름은 존이에요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"My name is John.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I from Korea.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I am a boy.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"나는 학생이에요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I am a student.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"My name is Sia.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I am a girl.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"나는 남자에요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I am a man.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I am a boy.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I am a woman.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"My name is Charles.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"내 이름은 찰스에요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"안녕하세요. 반갑습니다.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 한국에서 왔어요.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I am a student.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 학생입니다.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 남자에요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"저는 미국에서 왔어요.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I am a man.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 남자에요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"저는 여자에요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"저는 소년이에요.","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"name":"Level 3","stageID":3,"roundList":[{"sentence":"너는 이름이 뭐에요?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"What is your name?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"Nice to meet you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Hello.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"이것은 뭐에요?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"What is this?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"Hello.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"My name is John.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"What is your name?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"너는 이름이 뭐니?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"어디서 왔어요?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"이것은 뭐에요?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"What is this?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"이것은 뭐에요?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"제 이름은 시아에요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 발리에서 왔어요.","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"name":"Level 4","stageID":4,"roundList":[{"sentence":"나는 사과를 먹어요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I eat an apple.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I drink coffee.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I am a boy.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"나는 빵을 먹어요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I eat bread.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I have candy.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"My name is John.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"나는 사탕을 먹어요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I eat candy.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I eat apple.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I eat bread.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I eat apple.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 사과를 먹어요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 한국에서 왔어요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"안녕하세요.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I eat bread.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 빵을 먹어요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"내 이름은 빵입니다.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"만나서 반가워요.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I eat candy.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 사탕을 먹어요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"안녕하세요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 커피를 마셔요.","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"name":"Level 5","stageID":5,"roundList":[{"sentence":"나는 커피를 마셔요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I drink coffee.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I eat bread.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I eat apple.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"나는 물을 마셔요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I drink water.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I drink coffee.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I eat candy.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"나는 우유를 마셔요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I drink milk.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"She drinks coffee.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I drink coffee.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I drink coffee.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 커피를 마셔요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 사과를 먹어요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 빵을 먹어요.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I drink water.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 물을 마셔요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 커피를 마셔요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 우유를 마셔요.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I drink milk.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 우유를 마셔요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 스타벅스를 좋아해요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"그녀는 커피를 마셔요.","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"name":"Level 6","stageID":6,"roundList":[{"sentence":"나는 학교에 가요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I go to school.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I go to home.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I go to office.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I go to airport.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"나는 공항에 가요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I go to the airport.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I go to my home.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I go to the school.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I eat coffee.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"나는 집에 가요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I go to my home.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I go to airport.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I go to school.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I go to Starbucks.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I go to school.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 학교에 가요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"내 이름은 박시아입니다.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 사과를 먹어요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 커피를 마셔요.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I go to airport.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 공항에 가요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 학교에 가요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 집에 가요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 커피숍에 가요.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I go to Starbucks.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 스타벅스에 가요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 공항에 가요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 학교에 가요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 집에 가요.","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"name":"Level 7","stageID":7,"roundList":[{"sentence":"나는 책을 읽어요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I read a book.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I eat an apple.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I drink coffee.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I go to school.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"나는 신문을 읽어요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I read a newspaper.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I go school.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I drink water.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I read a book.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"나는 편지를 읽어요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I read a letter.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I read a book.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I read a newspaper.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I make a book.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I read a book.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 책을 읽어요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 커피를 마셔요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 빵을 먹어요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 학교에 가요.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I read a newspaper.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 신문을 읽어요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 책을 읽어요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 편지를 읽어요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 커피를 먹어요.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I read a letter.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 편지를 읽어요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 책을 읽어요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 커피를 만들어요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 신문을 읽어요.","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"name":"Level 8","stageID":8,"roundList":[{"sentence":"나는 친구를 만나요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I meet my friend.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I go to school.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I eat candy.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I read a book.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"나는 엄마를 만나요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I meet my mom.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I go school.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I drink coffee.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I meet my dad.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"나는 아빠를 만나요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I meet my dad.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I go school.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I meet my mom.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I meet my friend.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I meet my friend.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 친구를 만나요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 빵을 먹어요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 콜라를 마셔요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 학교에 가요.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I meet my mom.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 엄마를 만나요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 아빠를 만나요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 사과를 먹어요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 책을 읽어요.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I meet my dad.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 아빠를 만나요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 엄마를 만나요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 친구를 만나요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 공항에 가요.","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"name":"Level 9","stageID":9,"roundList":[{"sentence":"나는 케이크를 만들어요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I make a cake.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I go to school.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I meet my mom.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I eat cake.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"나는 책상을 만들어요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I make a table.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I make a cake.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I eat a cake.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I make coffee.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"나는 커피를 만들어요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I make coffee.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I make a cake.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I make a table.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I drink coffee.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I make a cake.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 케이크을 만들어요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 커피를 만들어요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 책생을 만들어요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 사탕 먹어요.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I make a table.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 책상을 만들어요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 커피를 만들어요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 케이크을 만들어요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 빵을 먹어요.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I make a coffee.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 커피를 만들어요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 케이크을 만들어요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 빵을 만들어요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 커피를 마셔요.","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"name":"Level 10","stageID":10,"roundList":[{"sentence":"나는 강아지를 좋아해요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I like dog.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I like coffee.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I go to airport.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I drink water.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"나는 고양이를 좋아해요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I like cat.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I make a cake.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I read a book.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I like dog.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"나는 원숭이를 좋아해요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I like monkey.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I like dog.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I like cat.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I like coffee.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I like dog.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 강아지를 좋아해요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 학교에 가요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 사과를 먹어요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 책을 읽어요.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I like cat.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 고양이를 좋아해요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 빵을 먹어요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 공항에 가요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 책을 읽어요.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I like monkey.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 원숭이를 좋아해요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 고양이를 좋아해요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 강아지를 좋아해요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 커피를 좋아해요.","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"name":"Level 11","stageID":11,"roundList":[{"sentence":"나는 샤워를 싫어해요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I hate to take a shower.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I hate homework.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I go to school.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I eat an apple.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"나는 숙제를 싫어해요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I hate homework.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I eat a bread.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I go to the airport.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I like to take a shower.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"나는 공부를 싫어해요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I hate study.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I hate to take a shower.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I like study.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I don't homework.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I hate shower.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 샤워를 싫어해요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 고양이를 싫어해요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 빵을 먹어요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 학교에 가요.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I hate homework.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 숙제를 싫어해요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 고양이를 싫어해요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 강아지를 싫어해요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 샤워를 싫어해요.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I hate study.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 공부를 싫어해요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 숙제를 싫어해요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 샤워를 싫어해요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 공부를 좋아해요.","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"name":"Level 12","stageID":12,"roundList":[{"sentence":"나는 너를 사랑해요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I love you.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I love coffee.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I love dog.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I love cat.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"나는 커피를 사랑해요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I love coffee.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I love dog.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I love you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I drink coffee.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"나는 강아지를 사랑해요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I love dog.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I love coffee.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I love you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I like cat.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I love you.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 너를 사랑해요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 커피를 사랑해요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 강아지를 좋아해요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 커피를 마셔요.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I love coffee.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 커피를 사랑해요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 너를 사랑해요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 커피를 마셔요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 사과를 먹어요.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I love dog.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 강아지를 사랑해요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 너를 사랑해요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 고양이를 사랑해요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 너를 사랑해요.","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"name":"Level 13","stageID":13,"roundList":[{"sentence":"너는 닭고기를 먹니?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"Do you eat chicken.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"Do you eat a bread.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Do you eat a candy.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"너는 소고기를 먹니?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"Do you eat a beef.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"Do you eat apple.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Do you eat a candy.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"너는 돼지고기를 먹니?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"Do you eat a pork.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"Do you eat a bread.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Do you eat apple.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"Do you eat chicken.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"너는 닭고기를 먹니?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"너는 빵을 먹니?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"너는 사탕을 먹니?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"Do you eat a beef.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"너는 소고기를 먹니?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"너는 사과를 먹니?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"너는 사탕을 먹니?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"Do you eat a pork.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"너는 돼지고기를 먹니?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"너는 사과를 먹니?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"너는 빵을 먹니?","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"name":"Level 14","stageID":14,"roundList":[{"sentence":"너는 차를 마시니?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"Do you eat tea?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"Do you eat water?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Do you eat milk?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"너는 주스를 마시니?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"Do you eat juice?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"Do you eat milk?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Do you eat coffee?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"너는 국을 마시니?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"Do you eat soup?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"Do you eat water?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Do you eat coffee?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"Do you drink tea?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"너는 차를 마시니?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"너는 물을 마시니?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"너는 우유를 마시니?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"Do you drink juice?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"너는 주스를 마시니?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"너는 커피를 마시니?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"너는 우유를 마시니?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"Do you drink soup?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"너는 국을 마시니?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"너는 커피를 마시니?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"너는 물을 마시니?","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"name":"Level 15","stageID":15,"roundList":[{"sentence":"너는 학교에 가니?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"Do you go to school?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"Do you go to airport?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Do you go to your home?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"너는 공항에 가니?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"Do you go to airport?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"Do you go to school?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Do you go to your home?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"너는 집에 가니?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"Do you go to your home?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"Do you go to airport?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Do you go to school?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"Do you go to school?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"너는 학교에 가니?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"너는 공항에 가니?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"너는 집에 가니?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"Do you go to airport?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"너는 공항에 가니?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"너는 학교에 가니?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"너는 집에 가니?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"Do you go to your home?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"너는 집에 가니?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"너는 공항에 가니?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"너는 학교에 가니?","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"name":"Level 16","stageID":16,"roundList":[{"sentence":"너는 책을 읽니?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"Do you read a book?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"Do you read a newspaper?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Do you read a letter?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"너는 신문을 읽니?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"Do you read a newspaper?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"Do you read a book?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Do you read a letter?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"너는 편지를 읽니?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"Do you read a letter?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"Do you read a newspaper?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Do you read a book?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"Do you read a book?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"너는 책을 읽니?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"너는 신문을 읽니?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"너는 편지를 읽니?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"Do you read a newspaper?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"너는 신문을 읽니?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"너는 책을 읽니?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"너는 편지를 읽니?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"Do you read a letter?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"너는 편지를 읽니?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"너는 책을 읽니?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"너는 신문을 읽니?","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"name":"Level 17","stageID":17,"roundList":[{"sentence":"너는 친구를 만나니?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"Do you meet your friend?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"Do you meet your mom?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Do you meet your dad?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"너는 엄마를 만나니?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"Do you meet your mom?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"Do you meet your friend?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Do you meet your dad?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"너는 아빠를 만나니?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"Do you meet your dad?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"Do you meet your mom?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Do you meet your friend?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"Do you meet your friend?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"너는 친구를 만나니?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"너는 엄마를 만나니?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"너는 아빠를 만나니?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"Do you meet your mom?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"너는 엄마를 만나니?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"너는 친구를 만나니?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"너는 아빠를 만나니?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"Do you meet your dad?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"너는 아빠를 만나니?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"너는 엄마를 만나니?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"너는 친구를 만나니?","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"name":"Level 18","stageID":18,"roundList":[{"sentence":"너는 케이크를 만드니?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"Do you make a cake?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"Do you make a table?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Do you make a coffee?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"너는 책상을 만드니?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"Do you make a table?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"Do you make a cake?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Do you make a coffee?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"너는 커피를 만드니?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"Do you make a coffee?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"Do you make a cake?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Do you make a table?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"Do you make a cake?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"너는 케이크를 만드니?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"너는 책상을 만드니?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"너는 빵을 만드니?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"Do you make a table?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"너는 책상을 만드니?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"너는 케이크를 만드니?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"너는 커피를 만드니?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"Do you make a coffee?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"너는 커피를 만드니?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"너는 커피를 마시니?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"너는 케이크를 만드니?","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"name":"Level 19","stageID":19,"roundList":[{"sentence":"너는 강아지를 좋아하니?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"Do you like dog?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"Do you like cat?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Do you like monkey?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"너는 고양이를 좋아하니?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"Do you like cat?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"Do you like dog?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Do you like monkey?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"너는 원숭이를 좋아하니?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"Do you like monkey?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"Do you like cat?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Do you like dog?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"Do you like dog?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"너는 강아지를 좋아하니?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"너는 고양이를 좋아하니?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"너는 원숭이를 좋아하니?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"Do you like cat?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"너는 고양이를 좋아하니?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"너는 원숭이를 좋아하니?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"너는 강아지를 좋아하니?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"Do you like monkey?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"너는 원숭이를 좋아하니?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"너는 고양이를 좋아하니?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"너는 강아지를 좋아하니?","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"name":"Level 20","stageID":20,"roundList":[{"sentence":"너는 사워를 싫어하니?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"Do you hate shower?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"Do you hate homework?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Do you hate study?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"너는 숙제를 싫어하니?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"Do you hate homework?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"Do you hate shower?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Do you hate study?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"너는 공부를 싫어하니?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"Do you hate study?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"Do you hate shower?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Do you hate homework?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"Do you hate shower?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"너는 사워를 싫어하니?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"너는 공부를 싫어하니?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"너는 숙제를 싫어하니?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"Do you hate homework?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"너는 숙제를 싫어하니?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"너는 공부를 싫어하니?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"너는 사워를 싫어하니?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"Do you hate study?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"너는 공부를 싫어하니?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"너는 숙제를 싫어하니?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"너는 사워를 싫어하니?","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"name":"Level 21","stageID":21,"roundList":[{"sentence":"너는 나를 사랑하니?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"Do you love me?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"Do you love coffe?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Do you love dog?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"너는 커피를 사랑하니?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"Do you love coffe?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"Do you love me?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Do you love dog?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"너는 강아지를 사랑하니?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"Do you love dog?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"Do you love me?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Do you love coffe?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"Do you love me?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"너는 나를 좋아하니?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"너는 커피를 좋아하니?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"너는 강아지를 좋아하니?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"Do you love coffe?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"너는 커피를 좋아하니?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"너는 강아지를 좋아하니?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"너는 나를 좋아하니?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"Do you love dog?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"너는 강아지를 좋아하니?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"너는 커피를 좋아하니?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"너는 나를 좋아하니?","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"name":"Level 22","stageID":22,"roundList":[{"sentence":"나는 사과를 안 먹어요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I do not eat an apple.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I do not eat a bread.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I do not eat a candy.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"나는 빵을 안 먹어요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I do not eat a bread.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I do not eat an apple.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I do not eat a candy.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"나는 사탕을 안 먹어요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I do not eat a candy.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I do not eat a bread.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I do not eat an apple.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I do not eat an apple.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 사과를 안 먹어요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 빵을 안 먹어요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 사탕을 안 먹어요.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I do not eat a bread.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 빵을 안 먹어요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 사탕을 안 먹어요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 사과를 안 먹어요.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I do not eat a candy.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 사탕을 안 먹어요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 빵을 안 먹어요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 사과를 안 먹어요.","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"name":"Level 23","stageID":23,"roundList":[{"sentence":"나는 커피를 안 마셔요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I do not drink coffee.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I do not drink milk.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I do not drink water.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"나는 우유를 안 마셔요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I do not drink milk.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I do not drink coffee.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I do not drink water.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"나는 물을 안 마셔요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I do not drink water.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I do not drink coffee.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I do not drink milk.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I do not drink coffee.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 커피를 안 마셔요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 물을 안 마셔요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 우유를 안 마셔요.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I do not drink milk.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 우유를 안 마셔요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 물을 안 마셔요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 커피를 안 마셔요.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I do not drink water.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 물을 안 마셔요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 우유를 안 마셔요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 커피를 안 마셔요.","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"name":"Level 24","stageID":24,"roundList":[{"sentence":"나는 학교에 안 가요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I do not go to school.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I do not go to airport.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I do not go to my home.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"나는 공항에 안 가요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I do not go to airport.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I do not go to school.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I do not go to my home.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"나는 집에 안 가요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"Translate this sentence.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I do not go to school.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I do not go to airport.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I do not go to school.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 학교에 안 가요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 공항에 안 가요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 집에 안 가요.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I do not go to airport.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 공항에 안 가요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 집에 안 가요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 학교에 안 가요.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I do not go to my home.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 집에 안 가요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 공항에 안 가요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 학교에 안 가요.","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"name":"Level 25","stageID":25,"roundList":[{"sentence":"나는 책을 안 읽어요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I do not read a book.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I do not read a newspaper.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I do not read a letter.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"나는 신문을 안 읽어요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I do not read a newspaper.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I do not read a book.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I do not read a letter.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"나는 편지를 안 읽어요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I do not read a letter.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I do not read a newspaper.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I do not read a book.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I do not read a book.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 책을 안 읽어요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 신문을 안 읽어요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 편지를 안 읽어요.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I do not read a newspaper.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 신문을 안 읽어요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 편지를 안 읽어요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 책을 안 읽어요.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I do not read a letter.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 편지를 안 읽어요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 신문을 안 읽어요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 책을 안 읽어요.","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"name":"Level 26","stageID":26,"roundList":[{"sentence":"나는 친구를 안 만나요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I do not meet my friend.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I do not meet my mom.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I do not meet my dad.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"나는 엄마를 안 만나요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"Translate this sentence.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I do not meet my dad.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I do not meet my friend.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"나는 아빠를 안 만나요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I do not meet my dad.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I do not meet my friend.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I do not meet my mom.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I do not meet my friend.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 친구를 안 만나요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 엄마를 안 만나요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 아빠를 안 만나요.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I do not meet my mom.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 엄마를 안 만나요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 아빠를 안 만나요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 친구를 안 만나요.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I do not meet my dad.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 아빠를 안 만나요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 엄마를 안 만나요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 친구를 안 만나요.","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"name":"Level 27","stageID":27,"roundList":[{"sentence":"나는 케이크를 안 만들어요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I do not make a cake.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I do not make a table.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I do not make a coffee.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"나는 책상을 안 만들어요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I do not make a table.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I do not make a cake.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I do not make a coffee.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"나는 커피를 안 만들어요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I do not make a coffee.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I do not make a table.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I do not make a cake.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I do not make a cake.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 케이크를 안 만들어요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 책상을 안 만들어요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 커피를 안 만들어요.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I do not make a table.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 책상을 안 만들어요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 커피를 안 만들어요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 케이크를 안 만들어요.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I do not make a coffee.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 커피를 안 만들어요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 책상을 안 만들어요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 케이크를 안 만들어요.","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"name":"Level 28","stageID":28,"roundList":[{"sentence":"나는 강아지를 안 좋아해요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I do not like dog.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I do not like cat.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I do not like coffee.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"나는 고양이를 안 좋아해요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I do not like cat.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I do not like dog.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I do not like coffee.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"나는 커피를 안 좋아해요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I do not like coffee.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I do not like cat.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I do not like dog.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I do not like dog.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 강아지를 안 좋아해요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 고양이를 안 좋아해요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 커피를 안 좋아해요.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I do not like cat.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 고양이를 안 좋아해요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 커피를 안 좋아해요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 강아지를 안 좋아해요.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I do not like coffee.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 커피를 안 좋아해요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 고양이를 안 좋아해요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 강아지를 안 좋아해요.","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"name":"Level 29","stageID":29,"roundList":[{"sentence":"나는 샤워를 안 싫어해요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I do not hate shower.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I do not hate homework.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I do not hate study.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"나는 숙제를 안 싫어해요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I do not hate homework.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I do not hate shower.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I do not hate study.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"나는 공부를 안 싫어해요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I do not hate study.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I do not hate homework.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I do not hate shower.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I do not hate shower.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 샤워를 안 싫어해요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 공부를 안 싫어해요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 숙제를 안 싫어해요.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I do not hate homework.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 공부를 안 싫어해요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 숙제를 안 싫어해요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 샤워를 안 싫어해요.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I do not hate study.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 공부를 안 싫어해요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 숙제를 안 싫어해요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 샤워를 안 싫어해요.","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"name":"Level 30","stageID":30,"roundList":[{"sentence":"나는 커피를 사랑하지 않아요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I do not love coffee.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I do not love dog.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I do not love you.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"나는 강아지를 사랑하지 않아요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I do not love dog.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I do not love coffee.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I do not love you.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"나는 너를 사랑하지 않아요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I do not love you.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I do not love dog.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I do not love coffee.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I do not love coffee.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 커피를 사랑하지 않아요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 강아지를 사랑하지 않아요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 너를 사랑하지 않아요.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I do not love dog.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 강아지를 사랑하지 않아요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 커피를 사랑하지 않아요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 너를 사랑하지 않아요.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I do not love you.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 너를 사랑하지 않아요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 강아지 사랑하지 않아요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 커피를 사랑하지 않아요.","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"name":"Level 31","stageID":31,"roundList":[{"sentence":"나는 아침을 먹을 거에요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I will eat breakfast.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I will eat lunch.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I will eat dinner.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"나는 점심을 먹을 거에요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I will eat lunch.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I will eat breakfast.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I will eat dinner.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"나는 저녁을 먹을 거에요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I will eat dinner.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I will eat lunch.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I will eat breakfast.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I will eat breakfast.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 아침을 먹을 거에요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 점심을 먹을 거에요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 저녁을 먹을 거에요.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I will eat lunch.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 점심을 먹을 거에요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 아침을 먹을 거에요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 점심을 먹을 거에요.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I will eat dinner.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 저녁을 먹을 거에요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 아침을 먹을 거에요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 점심을 먹을 거에요.","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"name":"Level 32","stageID":32,"roundList":[{"sentence":"나는 커피를 마실 거에요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I will drink coffee.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I will drink water.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I will drink milk.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"나는 물을 마실 거에요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I will drink water.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I will drink coffee.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I will drink milk.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"나는 우유를 마실 거에요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I will drink milk.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I will drink water.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I will drink coffee.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I will drink coffee.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 커피를 마실 거에요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 물을 마실 거에요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 우유를 마실 거에요.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I will drink water.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 물을 마실 거에요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 커피를 마실 거에요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 우유를 마실 거에요.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I will drink milk.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 우유를 마실 거에요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 커피를 마실 거에요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 물을 마실 거에요.","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"name":"Level 33","stageID":33,"roundList":[{"sentence":"나는 회사에 갈 거에요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I will go to company.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I will go to hospital.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I will go to bank.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"나는 병원에 갈 거에요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I will go to hospital.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I will go to company.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I will go to bank.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"나는 은행에 갈 거에요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I will go to bank.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I will go to hospital.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I will go to company.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I will go to company.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 회사에 갈 거에요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 병원에 갈 거에요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 은행에 갈 거에요.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I will go to hospital.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 병원에 갈 거에요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 회사에 갈 거에요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 병원에 갈 거에요.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I will go to bank.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 은행에 갈 거에요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 회사에 갈 거에요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 병원에 갈 거에요.","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"name":"Level 34","stageID":34,"roundList":[{"sentence":"나는 책을 읽을 거에요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I will read a book.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I will read a newspater.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I will read a letter.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"나는 신문을 읽을 거에요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I will read a newspater.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I will read a book.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I will read a letter.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"나는 편지를 읽을 거에요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I will read a letter.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I will read a newspater.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I will read a book.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I will read a book.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 책을 읽을 거에요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 신문을 읽을 거에요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 편지를 읽을 거에요.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I will read a newspater.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 신문을 읽을 거에요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 책을 읽을 거에요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 편지를 읽을 거에요.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I will read a letter.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 편지를 읽을 거에요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 신문을 읽을 거에요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 책을 읽을 거에요.","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"name":"Level 35","stageID":35,"roundList":[{"sentence":"나는 동생을 만날 거에요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I will meet young brother.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I will meet old sister.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I will meet old brother.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"나는 언니를 만날 거에요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I will meet old sister.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I will meet young brother.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I will meet old brother.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"나는 오빠를 만날 거에요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I will meet old brother.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I will meet old sister.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I will meet young brother.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I will meet young brother.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 동생을 만날 거에요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 언니를 만날 거에요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 오빠를 만날 거에요.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I will meet old sister.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 언니를 만날거에요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 동생을 만날거에요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 형을 만날거에요.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I will meet old brother.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 오빠를 만날거에요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 언니를 만날거에요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 동생을 만날거에요.","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"name":"Level 36","stageID":36,"roundList":[{"sentence":"나는 집을 만들 거에요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I will make house.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I will make building.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I will make road.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"나는 건물을 만들 거에요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I will make building.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I will make house.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I will make road.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"나는 길을 만들 거에요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I will make road.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I will make building.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I will make house.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I will make house.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 집을 만들 거에요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 건물을 만들 거에요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 길을 만들 거에요.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I will make building.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 건물을 만들 거에요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 집을 만들 거에요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 길을 만들 거에요.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I will make road.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 길을 만들 거에요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 건물을 만들 거에요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 집을 만들 거에요.","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"name":"Level 37","stageID":37,"roundList":[{"sentence":"나는 바다를 좋아할 거에요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I will like sea.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I will like mountain.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I will like river.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"나는 산을 좋아할 거에요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I will like mountain.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I will like sea.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I will like river.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"나는 강을 좋아할 거에요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I will like river.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I will like sea.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I will like mountain.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I will like sea.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 바다를 좋아할 거에요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 산을 좋아할 거에요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 강을 좋아할 거에요.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I will like mountain.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 산을 좋아할 거에요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 바다를 좋아할 거에요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 강을 좋아할 거에요.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I will like river.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 강을 좋아할 거에요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 산을 좋아할 거에요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 바다를 좋아할 거에요.","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"name":"Level 38","stageID":38,"roundList":[{"sentence":"나는 영어를 싫어할 거에요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I will hate english.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I will hate math.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I will hate science.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"나는 수학을 싫어할 거에요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I will hate math.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I will hate english.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I will hate science.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"나는 과학을 싫어할 거에요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I will hate science.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I will hate math.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I will hate english.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I will hate english.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 영어를 싫어할 거에요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 수학을 싫어할 거에요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 과학을 싫어할 거에요.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I will hate math.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 수학을 싫어할 거에요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 영어를 싫어할 거에요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 과학을 싫어할 거에요.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I will hate science.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 과학을 싫어할 거에요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 수학을 싫어할 거에요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 영어를 싫어할 거에요.","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"name":"Level 39","stageID":39,"roundList":[{"sentence":"나는 서울을 사랑할 거에요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I will love Seoul.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I will love Bail.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I will love Osaka.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"나는 발리를 사랑할 거에요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I will love Bail.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I will love Seoul.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I will love Osaka.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"나는 오사카를 사랑할 거에요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I will love Osaka.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I will love Bail.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I will love Seoul.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I will love Seoul.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 서울을 사랑할 거에요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 발리를 사랑할 거에요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 오사카를 사랑할 거에요.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I will love Bail.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 발리를 사랑할 거에요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 서울을 사랑할 거에요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 오사카를 사랑할 거에요.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I will love Osaka.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 오사카를 사랑할 거에요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 발리를 사랑할 거에요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 서울을 사랑할 거에요.","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"name":"Level 40","stageID":40,"roundList":[{"sentence":"너는 피자를 먹을 거니?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"Will you eat pizza?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"Will you eat hamburger?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Will you eat ramen?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"너는 햄버그를 먹을 거니?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"Will you eat hamburger?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"Will you eat pizza?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Will you eat ramen?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"너는 라면을 먹을 거니?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"Will you eat ramen?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"Will you eat hamburger?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Will you eat pizza?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"Will you eat pizza?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"너는 피자를 먹을 거니?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"너는 햄버그를 먹을 거니?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"너는 라면을 먹을 거니?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"Will you eat hamburger?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"너는 햄버그를 먹을 거니?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"너는 피자를 먹을 거니?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"너는 라면을 먹을 거니?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"Will you eat ramen?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"너는 라면을 먹을 거니?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"너는 햄버그를 먹을 거니?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"너는 피자를 먹을 거니?","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"name":"Level 41","stageID":41,"roundList":[{"sentence":"너 카페라떼 먹을래?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"Will you drink cafe latte?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"Will you drink caramel machiato?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Will you drink mocha latte?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"너 카라멜 마키아토 먹을래?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"Will you drink caramel machiato?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"Will you drink cafe latte?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Will you drink mocha latte?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"너 모카 라떼 먹을래?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"Will you drink mocha latte?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"Will you drink caramel machiato?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Will you drink cafe latte?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"Will you drink cafe latte?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"너 카페라떼 먹을래?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"너 카라멜 마키아토 먹을래?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"너 모카 라떼 먹을래?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"Will you drink caramel machiato?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"너 카라멜 마키아토 먹을래?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"너 카페라떼 먹을래?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"너 모카 라떼 먹을래?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"Will you drink mocha latte?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"너 모카 라떼 먹을래?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"너 카라멜 마키아토 먹을래?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"너 카페라떼 먹을래?","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"name":"Level 42","stageID":42,"roundList":[{"sentence":"너는 한국에 갈거니?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"Will you go to Korea?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"Will you go to America?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Will you go to China?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"너는 미국에 갈거니?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"Will you go to America?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"Will you go to Korea?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Will you go to China?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"너는 중국에 갈거니?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"Will you go to China?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"Will you go to America?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Will you go to Korea?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"Will you go to Korea?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"너는 한국에 갈거니?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"너는 미국에 갈거니?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"너는 중국에 갈거니?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"Will you go to America?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"너는 미국에 갈거니?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"너는 한국에 갈거니?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"너는 중국에 갈거니?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"Will you go to China?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"너는 중국에 갈거니?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"너는 미국에 갈거니?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"너는 한국에 갈거니?","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"name":"Level 43","stageID":43,"roundList":[{"sentence":"너는 차가 있을까?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"Will you have a car?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"Will you have a girlfriend?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Will you have a boyfriend?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"너는 여자친구가 있을까?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"Will you have a girlfriend?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"Will you have a car?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Will you have a boyfriend?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"너는 남자친구가 있을까?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"Will you have a boyfriend?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"Will you have a girlfriend?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Will you have a car?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"Will you have a car?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"너는 차가 있을까?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"너는 여자친구가 있을까?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"너는 남자친구가 있을까?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"Will you have a girlfriend?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"너는 여자친구가 있을까?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"너는 차가 있을까?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"너는 남자친구가 있을까?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"Will you have a boyfriend?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"너는 남자친구가 있을까?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"너는 여자친구가 있을까?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"너는 차가 있을까?","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"name":"Level 44","stageID":44,"roundList":[{"sentence":"너는 영화를 볼 거니?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"Will you watch a movie?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"Will you watch a drama?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Will you watch a TV?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"너는 드라마를 볼 거니?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"Will you watch a drama?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"Will you watch a movie?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Will you watch a TV?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"너는 티비를 볼 거니?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"Will you watch a TV?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"Will you watch a drama?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Will you watch a movie?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"Will you watch a movie?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"너는 영화를 볼 거니?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"너는 드라마를 볼 거니?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"너는 티비를 볼 거니?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"Will you watch a drama?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"너는 드라마를 볼 거니?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"너는 영화를 볼 거니?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"너는 티비를 볼 거니?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"Will you watch a TV?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"너는 티비를 볼 거니?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"너는 드라마를 볼 거니?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"너는 영화를 볼 거니?","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"name":"Level 45","stageID":45,"roundList":[{"sentence":"너 여기에 올 거니?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"Will you come here?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"Will you come to myhome?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Will you come to myoffice?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"너 우리집에 올 거니?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"Will you come to myhome?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"Will you come here?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Will you come to myoffice?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"너 내사무실에 올 거니?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"Will you come to myoffice?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"Will you come to myhome?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Will you come here?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"Will you come here?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"너 여기에 올 거니?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"너 우리집에 올 거니?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"너 내사무실에 올 거니?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"Will you come to myhome?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"너 우리집에 올 거니?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"너 여기에 올 거니?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"너 내사무실에 올 거니?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"Will you come to myoffice?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"너 내사무실에 올 거니?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"너 우리집에 올 거니?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"너 여기에 올 거니?","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"name":"Level 46","stageID":46,"roundList":[{"sentence":"너는 차를 살거니?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"Will you buy car?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"Will you buy motorcycle?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Will you buy bicycle?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"너는 오토바이를 살거니?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"Will you buy motorcycle?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"Will you buy car?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Will you buy bicycle?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"너는 자전거를 살거니?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"Will you buy bicycle?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"Will you buy motorcycle?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Will you buy car?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"Will you buy car?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"너는 차를 살거니?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"너는 오토바이를 살거니?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"너는 자전거를 살거니?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"Will you buy motorcycle?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"너는 오토바이를 살거니?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"너는 차를 살거니?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"너는 자전거를 살거니?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"Will you buy bicycle?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"너는 자전거를 살거니?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"너는 오토바이를 살거니?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"너는 차를 살거니?","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"name":"Level 47","stageID":47,"roundList":[{"sentence":"너 차를 팔 거니?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"Will you sell car?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"Will you sell motorcycle?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Will you sell bicycle?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"너 오토바이를 팔 거니?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"Will you sell motorcycle?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"Will you sell car?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Will you sell bicycle?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"너 자전거를 팔 거니?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"Will you sell bicycle?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"Will you sell motorcycle?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Will you sell car?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"Will you sell car?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"너 차를 팔 거니?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"너 오토바이를 팔 거니?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"너 자전거를 팔 거니?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"Will you sell motorcycle?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"너 오토바이를 팔 거니?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"너 차를 팔 거니?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"너 자전거를 팔 거니?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"Will you sell bicycle?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"너 자전거를 팔 거니?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"너 오토바이를 팔 거니?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"너 차를 팔 거니?","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"name":"Level 48","stageID":48,"roundList":[{"sentence":"너 팬 쓸 거니?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"Will you use a pen?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"Will you use a phone?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Will you use money?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"너 폰 쓸 거니?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"Will you use a phone?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"Will you use a pen?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Will you use money?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"너 돈 쓸 거니?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"Will you use money?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"Will you use a phone?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Will you use a pen?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"Will you use a pen?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"너 팬 쓸 거니?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"너 폰 쓸 거니?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"너 돈 쓸 거니?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"Will you use a phone?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"너 폰 쓸 거니?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"너 팬 쓸 거니?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"너 돈 쓸 거니?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"Will you use money?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"너 돈 쓸 거니?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"너 폰 쓸 거니?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"너 팬 쓸 거니?","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"name":"Level 49","stageID":49,"roundList":[{"sentence":"나는 쿠키 안 먹을거에요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I will not eat cookie.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I will not eat snack.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I will not eat toast.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"나는 과자 안 먹을거에요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I will not eat snack.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I will not eat cookie.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I will not eat toast.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"나는 토스트 안 먹을거에요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I will not eat toast.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I will not eat snack.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I will not eat cookie.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I will not eat cookie.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 쿠키 안 먹을거에요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 과자 안 먹을거에요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 토스트 안 먹을거에요.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I will not eat snack.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 과자 안 먹을거에요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 쿠키 안 먹을거에요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 토스트 안 먹을거에요.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I will not eat toast.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 토스트 안 먹을거에요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 과자 안 먹을거에요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 쿠키 안 먹을거에요.","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"name":"Level 50","stageID":50,"roundList":[{"sentence":"난 커피 안 마실 거야.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I will not drink coffee.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I will not drink water.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I will not drink milk.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"난 물 안 마실 거야.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I will not drink water.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I will not drink coffee.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I will not drink milk.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"난 우유 안 마실 거야.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I will not drink milk.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I will not drink water.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I will not drink coffee.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I will not drink coffee.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"난 커피 안 마실 거야.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"난 물 안 마실 거야.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"난 우유 안 마실 거야.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I will not drink water.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"난 물 안 마실 거야.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"난 커피 안 마실 거야.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"난 우유 안 마실 거야.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I will not drink milk.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"난 우유 안 마실 거야.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"난 물 안 마실 거야.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"난 커피 안 마실 거야.","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"name":"Level 51","stageID":51,"roundList":[{"sentence":"난 학교에 안 갈거에요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I will not go to school.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I will not go to cinema.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I will not go to beach.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"난 극장에 안 갈거에요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I will not go to cinema.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I will not go to school.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I will not go to beach.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"난 바닷가 안 갈거에요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I will not go to beach.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I will not go to cinema.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I will not go to school.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I will not go to school.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"난 학교에 안 갈거에요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"난 극장에 안 갈거에요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"난 바닷가 안 갈거에요.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I will not go to cinema.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"난 극장에 안 갈거에요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"난 학교에 안 갈거에요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"난 바닷가 안 갈거에요.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I will not go to beach.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"난 바닷가 안 갈거에요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"난 극장에 안 갈거에요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"난 학교에 안 갈거에요.","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"name":"Level 52","stageID":52,"roundList":[{"sentence":"나는 돈이 없을 거에요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I will not have money.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I will not have a ticket.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I will not have a computer.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"나는 티켓이 없을 거에요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I will not have a ticket.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I will not have a computer.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I will not have money.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"나는 컴퓨터가 없을 거에요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I will not have a computer.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I will not have a ticket.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I will not have money.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I will not have money.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 돈이 없을 거에요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 티켓이 없을 거에요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 컴퓨터가 없을 거에요.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I will not have a ticket.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 티켓이 없을 거에요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 돈이 없을 거에요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 컴퓨터가 없을 거에요.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I will not have a computer.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 컴퓨터가 없을 거에요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 티켓이 없을 거에요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 돈이 없을 거에요.","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"name":"Level 53","stageID":53,"roundList":[{"sentence":"나는 너를 안 볼 거에요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I will not see you.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I will not see myfriend.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I will not see mybrother.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"나는 내친구를 안 볼 거에요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I will not see myfriend.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I will not see you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I will not see mybrother.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"나는 내동생을 안 볼 거에요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I will not see mybrother.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I will not see myfriend.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I will not see you.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I will not see you.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 너를 안 볼 거에요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 친구를 안 볼 거에요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 동생을 안 볼 거에요.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I will not see myfriend.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 친구를 안 볼 거에요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 너를 안 볼 거에요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 동생을 안 볼 거에요.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I will not see mybrother.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 내동생을 안 볼 거에요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 내친구를 안 볼 거에요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 너를 안 볼 거에요.","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"name":"Level 54","stageID":54,"roundList":[{"sentence":"나는 자동차를 안 살 거에요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I will not buy car.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I will not buy motorcycle.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I will not buy bicycle.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"나는 오토바이를 안 살 거에요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I will not buy motorcycle.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I will not buy bicycle.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I will not buy car.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"나는 자전거를 안 살 거에요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I will not buy bicycle.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I will not buy motorcycle.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I will not buy car.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I will not buy car.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 자동차를 안 살 거에요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 오토바이를 안 살 거에요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 자전거를 안 살 거에요.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I will not buy motorcycle.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 오토바이를 안 살 거에요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 자동차를 안 살 거에요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 자전거를 안 살 거에요.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I will not buy bicycle.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 자전거를 안 살 거에요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 오토바이를 안 살 거에요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 자동차를 안 살 거에요.","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"name":"Level 55","stageID":55,"roundList":[{"sentence":"나는 자동차를 안 팔 거에요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I will not sell car.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I will not sell motorcycle.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I will not sell bicycle.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"나는 오토바이를 안 팔 거에요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I will not sell motorcycle.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I will not sell bicycle.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I will not sell car.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"나는 자전거를 안 팔 거에요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I will not sell bicycle.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I will not sell motorcycle.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I will not sell car.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I will not sell car.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 자동차를 안 팔 거에요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 오토바이를 안 팔 거에요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 자전거를 안 팔 거에요.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I will not sell motorcycle.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 오토바이를 안 팔 거에요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 자동차를 안 팔 거에요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 자전거를 안 팔 거에요.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I will not sell bicycle.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 자전거를 안 팔 거에요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 오토바이를 안 팔 거에요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 자동차를 안 팔 거에요.","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"name":"Level 56","stageID":56,"roundList":[{"sentence":"나는 펜을 안 쓸 거야.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I will not use pen.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I will not use phone.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I will not use phone.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"나는 돈을 안 쓸 거야.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I will not use money.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I will not use pen.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I will not use phone.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"나는 폰을 안 쓸 거야.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I will not use phone.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I will not use money.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I will not use pen.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I will not use pen.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 펜을 안 쓸 거야.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 돈을 안 쓸 거야.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 폰을 안 쓸 거야.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I will not use money.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 돈을 안 쓸 거야.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 펜을 안 쓸 거야.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 폰을 안 쓸 거야.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I will not use phone.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 폰을 안 쓸 거야.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 돈을 안 쓸 거야.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 펜을 안 쓸 거야.","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"name":"Level 57","stageID":57,"roundList":[{"sentence":"나는 사과를 먹었어요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I ate an apple.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I ate a bread.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I ate a candy.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"나는 빵을 먹었어요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I ate a bread.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I ate an apple.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I ate a candy.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"나는 사탕을 먹었어요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I ate a candy.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I ate a bread.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I ate an apple.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I ate an apple.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 사과를 먹었어요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 빵을 먹었어요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 사탕을 먹었어요.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I ate a bread.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 빵을 먹었어요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 사과를 먹었어요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 사탕을 먹었어요.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I ate a candy.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 사탕을 먹었어요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 빵을 먹었어요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 사과를 먹었어요.","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"name":"Level 58","stageID":58,"roundList":[{"sentence":"나는 커피 마셨어요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I drank coffe.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I drank water.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I drank milk.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"나는 물을 마셨어요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I drank water.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I drank coffe.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I drank milk.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"나는 우유를 마셨어요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I drank milk.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I drank water.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I drank coffe.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I drank coffe.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 커피 마셨어요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 물을 마셨어요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 우유를 마셨어요.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I drank water.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 물을 마셨어요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 커피 마셨어요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 우유를 마셨어요.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I drank milk.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 우유를 마셨어요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 물을 마셨어요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 커피 마셨어요.","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"name":"Level 59","stageID":59,"roundList":[{"sentence":"나는 학교에 갔었다.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I went to school.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I went to cinema.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I went to airport.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"나는 극장에 갔었다.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I went to cinema.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I went to school.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I went to airport.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"나는 공항에 갔었다.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I went to airport.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I went to cinema.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I went to school.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I went to school.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 학교에 갔었다.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 극장에 갔었다.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 공항에 갔었다.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I went to cinema.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 극장에 갔었다.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 학교에 갔었다.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 공항에 갔었다.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I went to airport.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 공항에 갔었다.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 극장에 갔었다.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 학교에 갔었다.","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"name":"Level 60","stageID":60,"roundList":[{"sentence":"나는 책을 읽었다.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I readed a book.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I readed a newspaper.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I readed a letter.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"나는 신문을 읽었다.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I readed a newspaper.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I readed a book.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I readed a letter.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"나는 편지를 읽었다.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I readed a letter.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I readed a newspaper.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I readed a book.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I readed a book.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 책을 읽었다.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 신문을 읽었다.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 편지를 읽었다.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I readed a newspaper.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 신문을 읽었다.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 책을 읽었다.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 편지를 읽었다.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I readed a letter.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 편지를 읽었다.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 책을 읽었다.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 신문을 읽었다.","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"name":"Level 61","stageID":61,"roundList":[{"sentence":"나는 친구를 만났다.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I met my friend.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I met my mom.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I met my dad.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"나는 엄마를 만났다.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I met my mom.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I met my friend.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I met my dad.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"나는 아빠를 만났다.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I met my dad.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I met my mom.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I met my friend.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I met my friend.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 친구를 만났다.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 엄마를 만났다.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 아빠를 만났다.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I met my mom.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 엄마를 만났다.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 아빠를 만났다.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 친구를 만났다.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I met my dad.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 아빠를 만났다.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 엄마를 만났다.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 친구를 만났다.","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"name":"Level 62","stageID":62,"roundList":[{"sentence":"나는 케이크를 만들었다.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I made cake.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I made table.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I made coffee.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"나는 책상을 만들었다.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I made table.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I made cake.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I made coffee.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"나는 커피를 만들었다.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I made coffee.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I made table.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I made cake.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I made cake.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 케이크를 만들었다.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 책상을 만들었다.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 커피를 만들었다.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I made table.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 책상을 만들었다.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 케이크를 만들었다.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 커피를 만들었다.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I made coffee.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 커피를 만들었다.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 책상을 만들었다.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 케이크를 만들었다.","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"name":"Level 63","stageID":63,"roundList":[{"sentence":"나는 강아지를 좋아했다.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I liked dog.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I liked cat.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I liked monkey.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"나는 고양이를 좋아했다.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I liked cat.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I liked dog.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I liked monkey.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"나는 원숭이를 좋아했다.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I liked monkey.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I liked cat.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I liked dog.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I liked dog.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 강아지를 좋아했다.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 고양이를 좋아했다.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 원숭이를 좋아했다.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I liked cat.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 고양이를 좋아했다.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 강아지를 좋아했다.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 원숭이를 좋아했다.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I liked monkey.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 원숭이를 좋아했다.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 고양이를 좋아했다.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 강아지를 좋아했다.","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"name":"Level 64","stageID":64,"roundList":[{"sentence":"나는 샤워를 싫어했다.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I hated shower.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I hated homework.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I hated study.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"나는 숙제를 싫어했다.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I hated homework.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I hated shower.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I hated study.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"나는 공부를 싫어했다.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I hated study.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I hated homework.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I hated shower.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I hated shower.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 샤워를 싫어했다.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 숙제를 싫어했다.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 공부를 싫어했다.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I hated homework.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 숙제를 싫어했다.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 샤워를 싫어했다.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 공부를 싫어했다.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I hated study.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 공부를 싫어했다.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 숙제를 싫어했다.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 샤워를 싫어했다.","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"name":"Level 65","stageID":65,"roundList":[{"sentence":"나는 너를 사랑했다.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I loved you.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I loved dog.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I loved coffee.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"나는 강아지를 사랑했다.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I loved dog.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I loved coffee.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I loved you.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"나는 커피를 사랑했다.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I loved coffee.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I loved dog.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I loved you.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I loved you.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 너를 사랑했다.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 강아지를 사랑했다.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 커피를 사랑했다.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I loved dog.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 강아지를 사랑했다.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 너를 사랑했다.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 커피를 사랑했다.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I loved coffee.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 커피를 사랑했다.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 강아지를 사랑했다.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 너를 사랑했다.","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"name":"Level 66","stageID":66,"roundList":[{"sentence":"너는 바나나를 먹었니?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"Did you eat banana?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"Did you eat orange?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Did you eat pineapple?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"너는 오렌지를 먹었니?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"Did you eat orange?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"Did you eat banana?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Did you eat pineapple?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"너는 파인에플 먹었니?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"Did you eat pineapple?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"Did you eat orange?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Did you eat banana?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"Did you eat banana?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"너는 바나나를 먹었니?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"너는 오렌지를 먹었니?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"너는 파인에플 먹었니?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"Did you eat orange?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"너는 오렌지를 먹었니?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"너는 바나나를 먹었니?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"너는 파인에플 먹었니?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"Did you eat pineapple?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"너는 파인에플 먹었니?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"너는 오렌지를 먹었니?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"너는 바나나를 먹었니?","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"name":"Level 67","stageID":67,"roundList":[{"sentence":"너는 커피를 마셨니?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"Did you drink coffee?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"Did you drink water?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Did you drink juice?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"너는 물을 마셨니?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"Did you drink water?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"Did you drink juice?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Did you drink coffee?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"너는 주스 마셨니?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"Did you drink juice?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"Did you drink water?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Did you drink coffee?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"Did you drink coffee?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"너는 커피를 마셨니?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"너는 물을 마셨니?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"너는 주스 마셨니?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"Did you drink water?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"너는 물을 마셨니?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"너는 커피를 마셨니?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"너는 주스 마셨니?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"Did you drink juice?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"너는 주스 마셨니?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"너는 물을 마셨니?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"너는 커피를 마셨니?","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"name":"Level 68","stageID":68,"roundList":[{"sentence":"너는 학교에 갔었니?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"Did you go to school?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"Did you go to hospital?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Did you go to bank?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"너는 병원에 갔었니?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"Did you go to hospital?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"Did you go to school?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Did you go to bank?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"너는 은행에 갔었니?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"Did you go to bank?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"Did you go to hospital?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Did you go to school?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"Did you go to school?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"너는 학교에 갔었니?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"너는 병원에 갔었니?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"너는 은행에 갔었니?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"Did you go to hospital?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"너는 병원에 갔었니?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"너는 학교에 갔었니?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"너는 은행에 갔었니?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"Did you go to bank?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"너는 은행에 갔었니?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"너는 학교에 갔었니?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"너는 병원에 갔었니?","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"name":"Level 69","stageID":69,"roundList":[{"sentence":"너는 책을 읽었니?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"Did you read a book?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"Did you read a newspaper?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Did you read a letter?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"너는 신문을 읽었니?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"Did you read a newspaper?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"Did you read a book?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Did you read a letter?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"너는 편지를 읽었니?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"Did you read a letter?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"Did you read a newspaper?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Did you read a book?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"Did you read a book?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"너는 책을 읽었니?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"너는 신문을 읽었니?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"너는 편지를 읽었니?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"Did you read a newspaper?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"너는 신문을 읽었니?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"너는 책을 읽었니?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"너는 편지를 읽었니?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"Did you read a letter?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"너는 편지를 읽었니?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"너는 신문을 읽었니?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"너는 책을 읽었니?","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"name":"Level 70","stageID":70,"roundList":[{"sentence":"너는 친구를 만났니?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"Did you meet your friend?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"Did you meet your mom?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Did you meet your dad?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"너는 엄마를 만났니?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"Did you meet your mom?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"Did you meet your friend?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Did you meet your dad?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"너는 아빠를 만났니?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"Did you meet your dad?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"Did you meet your mom?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Did you meet your friend?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"Did you meet your friend?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"너는 친구를 만났니?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"너는 엄마를 만났니?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"너는 아빠를 만났니?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"Did you meet your mom?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"너는 엄마를 만났니?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"너는 친구를 만났니?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"너는 아빠를 만났니?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"Did you meet your dad?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"너는 아빠를 만났니?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"너는 엄마를 만났니?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"너는 친구를 만났니?","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"name":"Level 71","stageID":71,"roundList":[{"sentence":"너는 강아지를 좋아했니?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"Did you like dog?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"Did you like cat?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Did you like monkey?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"너는 고양이를 좋아했니?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"Did you like cat?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"Did you like dog?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Did you like monkey?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"너는 원숭이를 좋아했니?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"Did you like monkey?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"Did you like cat?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Did you like dog?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"Did you like dog?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"너는 강아지를 좋아했니?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"너는 고양이를 좋아했니?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"너는 원숭이를 좋아했니?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"Did you like cat?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"너는 고양이를 좋아했니?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"너는 강아지를 좋아했니?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"너는 원숭이를 좋아했니?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"Did you like monkey?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"너는 원숭이를 좋아했니?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"너는 고양이를 좋아했니?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"너는 강아지를 좋아했니?","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"name":"Level 72","stageID":72,"roundList":[{"sentence":"너는 샤워를 싫어했니?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"Did you hate shower?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"Did you hate homework?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Did you hate study?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"너는 숙제를 싫어했니?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"Did you hate homework?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"Did you hate shower?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Did you hate study?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"너는 공부를 싫어했니?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"Did you hate study?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"Did you hate homework?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Did you hate shower?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"Did you hate shower?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"너는 샤워를 싫어했니?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"너는 숙제를 싫어했니?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"너는 공부를 싫어했니?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"Did you hate homework?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"너는 숙제를 싫어했니?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"너는 샤워를 싫어했니?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"너는 공부를 싫어했니?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"Did you hate study?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"너는 공부를 싫어했니?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"너는 숙제를 싫어했니?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"너는 샤워를 싫어했니?","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"name":"Level 73","stageID":73,"roundList":[{"sentence":"너는 나를 사랑했니?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"Did you love me?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"Did you love her?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Did you love him?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"너는 그녀를 사랑했니?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"Did you love her?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"Did you love me?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Did you love him?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"너는 그를 사랑했니?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"Did you love him?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"Did you love her?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Did you love me?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"Did you love me?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"너는 나를 사랑했니?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"너는 그녀를 사랑했니?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"너는 그를 사랑했니?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"Did you love her?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"너는 그녀를 사랑했니?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"너는 나를 사랑했니?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"너는 그를 사랑했니?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"Did you love him?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"너는 그를 사랑했니?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"너는 그녀를 사랑했니?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"너는 나를 사랑했니?","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"name":"Level 74","stageID":74,"roundList":[{"sentence":"나는 사과를 먹지 않았어요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I didn't eat an apple.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I didn't eat a cookie.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I didn't eat a candy.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"나는 쿠키를 먹지 않았어요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I didn't eat a cookie.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I didn't eat an apple.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I didn't eat a candy.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"나는 사탕을 먹지 않았어요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I didn't eat a candy.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I didn't eat a cookie.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I didn't eat an apple.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I didn't eat an apple.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 사과를 먹지 않았어요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 쿠키를 먹지 않았어요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 사탕을 먹지 않았어요.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I didn't eat a cookie.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 쿠키를 먹지 않았어요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 사탕을 먹지 않았어요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 사과를 먹지 않았어요.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I didn't eat a candy.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 사탕을 먹지 않았어요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 쿠키를 먹지 않았어요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 사과를 먹지 않았어요.","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"name":"Level 75","stageID":75,"roundList":[{"sentence":"나는 커피를 마시지 않았어요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I didn't drink coffee.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I didn't drink water.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I didn't drink milk.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"나는 물을 마시지 않았어요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I didn't drink water.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I didn't drink milk.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I didn't drink coffee.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"나는 우유를 마시지 않았어요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I didn't drink milk.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I didn't drink coffee.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I didn't drink water.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I didn't drink coffee.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 커피를 마시지 않았어요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 물을 마시지 않았어요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 우유를 마시지 않았어요.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I didn't drink water.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 물을 마시지 않았어요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 우유를 마시지 않았어요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 커피를 마시지 않았어요.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I didn't drink milk.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 우유를 마시지 않았어요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 물을 마시지 않았어요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 커피를 마시지 않았어요.","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"name":"Level 76","stageID":76,"roundList":[{"sentence":"나는 학교에 가지 않았어요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I didn't go to school.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I didn't go to bank.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I didn't go to hotel.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"나는 은행에 가지 않았어요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I didn't go to bank.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I didn't go to school.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I didn't go to hotel.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"나는 호텔에 가지 않았어요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I didn't go to hotel.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I didn't go to bank.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I didn't go to school.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I didn't go to school.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 학교에 가지 않았어요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 은행에 가지 않았어요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 호텔에 가지 않았어요.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I didn't go to bank.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 은행에 가지 않았어요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 학교에 가지 않았어요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 호텔에 가지 않았어요.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I didn't go to hotel.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 호텔에 가지 않았어요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 은행에 가지 않았어요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 학교에 가지 않았어요.","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"name":"Level 77","stageID":77,"roundList":[{"sentence":"나는 메뉴를 읽지 않았어요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I didn't read a menu.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I didn't read a note.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I didn't read a document.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"나는 노트를 읽지 않았어요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I didn't read a note.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I didn't read a menu.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I didn't read a document.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"나는 문서를 읽지 않았어요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I didn't read a document.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I didn't read a note.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I didn't read a menu.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I didn't read a menu.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 메뉴를 읽지 않았어요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 노트를 읽지 않았어요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 문서를 읽지 않았어요.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I didn't read a note.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 노트를 읽지 않았어요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 문서를 읽지 않았어요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 메뉴를 읽지 않았어요.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I didn't read a document.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 노트를 읽지 않았어요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 문서를 읽지 않았어요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 메뉴를 읽지 않았어요.","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"name":"Level 78","stageID":78,"roundList":[{"sentence":"나는 친구를 만나지 않았어요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I didn't meet my friend.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I didn't meet my mom.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I didn't meet my dad.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"나는 엄마를 만나지 않았어요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I didn't meet my mom.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I didn't meet my friend.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I didn't meet my dad.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"나는 아빠를 만나지 않았어요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I didn't meet my dad.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I didn't meet my mom.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I didn't meet my friend.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I didn't meet my friend.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 친구를 만나지 않았어요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 엄마를 만나지 않았어요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 아빠를 만나지 않았어요.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I didn't meet my mom.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 엄마를 만나지 않았어요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 친구를 만나지 않았어요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 아빠를 만나지 않았어요.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I didn't meet my dad.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 아빠를 만나지 않았어요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 엄마를 만나지 않았어요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 친구를 만나지 않았어요.","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"name":"Level 79","stageID":79,"roundList":[{"sentence":"나는 케이크를 만들지 않았어요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I didn't make a cake.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I didn't make a table.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I didn't make a key.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"나는 책상을 만들지 않았어요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I didn't make a table.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I didn't make a cake.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I didn't make a key.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"나는 열쇠를 만들지 않았어요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I didn't make a key.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I didn't make a table.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I didn't make a cake.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I didn't make a cake.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 케이크를 만들지 않았어요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 책상을 만들지 않았어요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 열쇠를 만들지 않았어요.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I didn't make a table.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 책상을 만들지 않았어요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 케이크를 만들지 않았어요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 열쇠를 만들지 않았어요.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I didn't make a key.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 열쇠를 만들지 않았어요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 케이크를 만들지 않았어요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 책상을 만들지 않았어요.","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"name":"Level 80","stageID":80,"roundList":[{"sentence":"나는 강아지를 좋아하지 않았어요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I didn't like dog.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I didn't like cat.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I didn't like monkey.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"나는 고양이를 좋아하지 않았어요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I didn't like cat.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I didn't like dog.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I didn't like monkey.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"나는 원숭이를 좋아하지 않았어요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I didn't like monkey.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I didn't like cat.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I didn't like dog.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I didn't like dog.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 강아지를 좋아하지 않았어요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 고양이를 좋아하지 않았어요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 원숭이를 좋아하지 않았어요.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I didn't like cat.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 고양이를 좋아하지 않았어요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 강아지를 좋아하지 않았어요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 원숭이를 좋아하지 않았어요.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I didn't like monkey.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 원숭이를 좋아하지 않았어요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 고양이를 좋아하지 않았어요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 강아지를 좋아하지 않았어요.","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"name":"Level 81","stageID":81,"roundList":[{"sentence":"나는 샤워를 싫어하지 않았어요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I didn't hate shower.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I didn't hate homework.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I didn't hate study.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"나는 숙제를 싫어하지 않았어요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I didn't hate homework.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I didn't hate shower.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I didn't hate study.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"나는 공부를 싫어하지 않았어요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I didn't hate study.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I didn't hate homework.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I didn't hate shower.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I didn't hate shower.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 샤워를 싫어하지 않았어요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 숙제를 싫어하지 않았어요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 공부를 싫어하지 않았어요.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I didn't hate homework.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 숙제를 싫어하지 않았어요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 샤워를 싫어하지 않았어요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 공부를 싫어하지 않았어요.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I didn't hate study.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 공부를 싫어하지 않았어요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 숙제를 싫어하지 않았어요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 샤워를 싫어하지 않았어요.","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"name":"Level 82","stageID":82,"roundList":[{"sentence":"나는 너를 사랑하지 않았어요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I didn't love you.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I didn't love him.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I didn't love her.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"나는 그를 사랑하지 않았어요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I didn't love him.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I didn't love you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I didn't love her.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"나는 그녀를 사랑하지 않았어요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"I didn't love her.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I didn't love him.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I didn't love you.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I didn't love you.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 너를 사랑하지 않았어요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 그를 사랑하지 않았어요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 그녀를 사랑하지 않았어요.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I didn't love him.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 그를 사랑하지 않았어요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 너를 사랑하지 않았어요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 그녀를 사랑하지 않았어요.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I didn't love her.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 그녀를 사랑하지 않았어요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 그를 사랑하지 않았어요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 너를 사랑하지 않았어요.","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"name":"Level 83","stageID":83,"roundList":[{"sentence":"When we eat?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"우리 언제 먹어요?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"우리 언제 마셔요?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나 언제 먹어요?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"When i drink?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"우리 언제 먹어요?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나 언제 마셔요?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나 언제 먹어요?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"When you go?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"너 언제 가요?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나 언제 마셔요?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나 언제 먹어요?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"우리 언제 공부해요?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"When we study?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"When we eat?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"When we go?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"너 언제 와요?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"When you come?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"When we eat?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"When we go?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"나 언제 읽어요?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"When i read?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"When we eat?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"When we go?","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"name":"Level 84","stageID":84,"roundList":[{"sentence":"우리 어디서 먹어요?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"Where we eat?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"Where we drink?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Where we go?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"우리 어디서 마셔요?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"Where we drink?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"Where we eat?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Where we go?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"우리 어디서 가요?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"Where we go?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"Where we drink?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Where we eat?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"Where we eat?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"우리 어디서 먹어요?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"우리 어디서 마셔요?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"우리 어디서 가요?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"Where we drink?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"우리 어디서 마셔요?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"우리 어디서 먹어요?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"우리 어디서 가요?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"Where we go?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"우리 어디서 가요?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"우리 어디서 마셔요?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"우리 어디서 먹어요?","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"name":"Level 85","stageID":85,"roundList":[{"sentence":"우리 뭐 먹어요?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"What we eat?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"What we drink?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"What we buy?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"우리 뭐 마셔요?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"What we drink?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"What we eat?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"What we buy?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"우리 뭐 사요?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"What we buy?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"What we drink?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"What we eat?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"What we eat?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"우리 뭐 먹어요?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"우리 뭐 마셔요?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"우리 뭐 사요?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"What we drink?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"우리 뭐 마셔요?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"우리 뭐 먹어요?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"우리 뭐 사요?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"What we buy?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"우리 뭐 사요?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"우리 뭐 마셔요?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"우리 뭐 먹어요?","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"name":"Level 86","stageID":86,"roundList":[{"sentence":"어떻게 이거 먹어요?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"How do I eat this?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"How are you drinking?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"How can I go?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"어떻게 마셔요?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"How are you drinking?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"How can I go?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"How do I eat this?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"어떻게 갈 수 있어요?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"How can I go?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"How do I eat this?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"How are you drinking?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"How do I eat this?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"어떻게 이거 먹어요?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"어떻게 마셔요?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"어떻게 갈 수 있어요?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"How are you drinking?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"어떻게 마셔요?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"어떻게 이거 먹어요?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"어떻게 갈 수 있어요?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"How can I go?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"어떻게 갈 수 있어요?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"어떻게 마셔요?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"어떻게 이거 먹어요?","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"name":"Level 87","stageID":87,"roundList":[{"sentence":"우리 왜 먹어?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"Why we eat?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"Why we study?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Why you go now?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"우리 왜 공부해?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"Why we study?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"Why you go now?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Why we eat?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"너 왜 지금 가?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"Why you go now?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"Why we study?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Why we eat?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"Why we eat?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"우리 왜 먹어?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"우리 왜 공부해?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"너 왜 지금 가?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"Why we study?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"우리 왜 공부해?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"우리 왜 먹어?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"너 왜 지금 가?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"Why you go now?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"너 왜 지금 가?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"우리 왜 공부해?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"우리 왜 먹어?","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"name":"Level 88","stageID":88,"roundList":[{"sentence":"누가 이거 먹었어요?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"Who ate this?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"Who drank this?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Who leaved?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"누가 이거 마셨어요?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"Who drank this?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"Who ate this?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Who leaved?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"누가 갔어요?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"Who leaved?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"Who drank this?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Who ate this?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"Who ate this?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"누가 이거 먹었어요?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"누가 이거 마셨어요?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"누가 갔어요?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"Who drank this?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"누가 갔어요?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"누가 이거 마셨어요?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"누가 이거 먹었어요?","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"Who leaved?","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"누가 갔어요?","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"누가 이거 마셨어요?","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"누가 이거 먹었어요?","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"name":"Level 89","stageID":89,"roundList":[{"sentence":"아침.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"Morning","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"Lunch","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Dinner","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"점심.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"Lunch","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"Morning","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Dinner","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"저녁.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"Dinner","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"Morning","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Lunch","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"Morning","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"아침.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"점심.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"저녁.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"Lunch","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"점심.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"아침.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"저녁.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"Dinner","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"저녁.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"점심.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"아침.","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"name":"Level 92","stageID":92,"roundList":[{"sentence":"지금.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"Now.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"Next","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"다음.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"Next.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"Now.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"Now.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"지금.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"다음.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"Next.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"다음.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"지금.","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"name":"Level 92","stageID":92,"roundList":[{"sentence":"오늘.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"Today.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"Yesterday.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Tomorrow.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"어제.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"Yesterday.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"Today.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Tomorrow.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"내일.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"Tomorrow.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"Yesterday.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Today.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"Today.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"오늘.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"내일.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"어제.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"Yesterday.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"어제.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"오늘.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"내일.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"Tomorrow.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"내일.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"어제.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"오늘.","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"name":"Level 94","stageID":94,"roundList":[{"sentence":"이번주.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"this week","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"next week","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"last week","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"다음주.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"next week","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"this week","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"last week","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"지난주.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"last week","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"next week","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"this week","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"this week","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"이번주.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"다음주.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"지난주.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"next week","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"다음주.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"지난주.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"이번주.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"last week","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"지난주.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"다음주.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"이번주.","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"name":"Level 97","stageID":97,"roundList":[{"sentence":"이번달.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"this month.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"next month.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"last month. ","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"다음달.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"next month.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"last month. ","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"this month.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"지난달.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"last month. ","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"next month.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"this month.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"this month.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"이번달.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"다음달.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"지난달.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"next month.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"다음달.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"지난달.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"이번달.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"last month. ","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"지난달.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"다음달.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"이번달.","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"name":"Level 100","stageID":100,"roundList":[{"sentence":"올해.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"this year","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"next year","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"last year","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"내년.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"next year","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"this year","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"last year","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"작년.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"last year","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"next year","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"this year","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"this year","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"올해.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"내년.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"작년.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"next year","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"내년.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"올해.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"작년.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"last year","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"작년.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"내년.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"올해.","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"name":"Level 103","stageID":103,"roundList":[{"sentence":"I.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"너.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"당신.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"우리.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"You.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"너.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"우리.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"We.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"우리(저희).","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"너희.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"They.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"그들.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"우리.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"너.","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"name":"Level 104","stageID":104,"roundList":[{"sentence":"He.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"그.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"그녀.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"She.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"그녀.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"그.","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"name":"Level 105","stageID":105,"roundList":[{"sentence":"This.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"이것.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"저것.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"그것.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"it.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"그것.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"이것.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"저것.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"that.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"저것.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"이것.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"그것.","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"name":"Level 106","stageID":106,"roundList":[{"sentence":"old brother.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"오빠(형)","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"동생.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"누나.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"old sister.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"언니(누나)","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"동생.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"형.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"young brother.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"남동생.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"형.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"누나.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"young sister.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"여동생.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"난동생.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"오빠.","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"name":"Level 107","stageID":107,"roundList":[{"sentence":"Dad.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"아빠.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"엄마.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"Mom.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"엄마.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"아빠.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"할머니.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"할아버지.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"Grandmother.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"할아버지.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"엄마.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"아빠.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"Grandfather.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"할머니.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"엄마.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"할아버지.","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"name":"Level 108","stageID":108,"roundList":[{"sentence":"Baby.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"아기.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"엄마.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"오빠.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"Child.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"아이.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"할머니.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"할아버지.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"Boy.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"소년.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"아빠.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"누나.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"Girl.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"소녀.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"여자.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"남자.","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"name":"Level 109","stageID":109,"roundList":[{"sentence":"Miss. ","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"아가씨.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"오빠.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"아줌마.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"Mister. ","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"아저씨.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"누나.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"할머니.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"Mrs.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"아줌마.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"형.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"아저씨.","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"name":"Level 110","stageID":110,"roundList":[{"sentence":"일.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"1","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"10","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"100","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"1000","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"이.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"1","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"2","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"3","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"4","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"삼.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"1","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"2","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"3","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"4","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"사.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"1","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"2","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"3","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"4","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"오.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"5","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"6","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"7","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"8","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"육.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"5","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"6","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"7","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"8","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"칠.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"5","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"6","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"7","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"8","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"팔.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"8","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"9","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"10","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"11","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"구.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"8","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"9","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"10","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"11","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"십.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"8","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"9","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"10","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"11","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"name":"Level 111","stageID":111,"roundList":[{"sentence":"십.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"10","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"11","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"12","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"13","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"이십.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"20","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"21","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"22","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"23","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"삼십.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"30","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"31","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"32","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"33","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"사십.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"40","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"41","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"42","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"43","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"오십.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"50","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"60","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"70","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"80","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"육십일.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"61","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"62","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"63","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"64","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"칠십이.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"71","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"72","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"73","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"74","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"팔십삼.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"81","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"82","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"83","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"84","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"구십구.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"9","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"99","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"19","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"909","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"백.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"1","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"10","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"100","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"1000","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"name":"Level 112","stageID":112,"roundList":[{"sentence":"백.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"100","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"110","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"120","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"130","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"이백.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"200","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"210","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"220","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"230","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"삼백.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"300","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"310","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"320","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"330","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"사백.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"400","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"410","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"420","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"430","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"오백.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"500","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"600","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"700","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"800","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"육백십.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"610","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"620","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"630","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"640","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"칠백십이.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"711","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"712","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"713","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"714","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"팔백십삼.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"811","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"812","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"813","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"814","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"구백구십구.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"9","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"999","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"119","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"909","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"천.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"1","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"10","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"100","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"1000","isCorrect":true}]}]},{"name":"Level 113","stageID":113,"roundList":[{"sentence":"천.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"1000","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"100","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"10","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"1","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"만.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"10000","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"1000","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"100","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"10","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"십만.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"100000","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"10000","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"10","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"1","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"백만.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"1000000","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"10000","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"1000","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"100","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"천만.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"10000000","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"10000","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"1000","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"100","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"억.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"100000000","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"10000","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"1000","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"100","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"name":"Level 114","stageID":114,"roundList":[{"sentence":"하나.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"1","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"2","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"3","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"4","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"둘.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"1","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"2","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"3","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"4","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"셋.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"1","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"2","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"3","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"4","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"넷.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"1","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"2","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"3","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"4","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"다섯.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"5","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"6","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"7","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"8","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"여섯.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"5","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"6","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"7","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"8","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"일곱.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"5","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"6","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"7","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"8","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"여덟.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"5","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"6","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"7","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"8","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"아홉.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"9","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"10","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"11","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"12","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"열.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"9","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"10","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"11","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"12","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"name":"Level 115","stageID":115,"roundList":[{"sentence":"열.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"10","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"20","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"스물.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"20","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"30","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"서른.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"30","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"40","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"마흔.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"40","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"50","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"쉰.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"50","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"60","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"예순.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"60","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"70","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"일흔.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"70","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"80","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"여든.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"80","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"90","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"아흔.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"90","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"100","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"name":"Level 116","stageID":116,"roundList":[{"sentence":"I can do it.","question":"Translate this sentence.","answers":[{"answer":"나는 할 수 있다.","isCorrect":true}]}]}]